
//
// The file can be modified to add more questions
//

var quizQuestions = [
        {
            "question" : "Q1: Javascript is a _____________ language?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "Object-oriented",
                                    "High-level",
                                    "Assembly-language",
                                    "Object-based"
                                ],
            "correct" : "Object-based",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q2: The unordered collection of properties, each of which has a name and a value is called?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "String",
                                    "Object",
                                    "Serialized Object",
                                    "All of the above"
                                ],
            "correct" : "Object",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q3: var count = [1,,3]; What is the observation made?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "The omitted value takes undefined",
                                    "This results in an error",
                                    "This results in an exception",
                                    "None of the mentioned"
                                ],
            "correct" : "The omitted value takes undefined",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q4: The keyword or the property that you use to refer to an object through which they were invoked is?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "from",
                                    "to",
                                    "this",
                                    "object"
                                ],
            "correct" : "this",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q5: When does the function name become optional in JavaScript?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "When the function is defined as a looping statement",
                                    "When the function is defined as expressions",
                                    "When the function is predefined",
                                    "All of above"
                                ],
            "correct" : "When the function is defined as expressions",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q6: What is the purpose of a return statement in a function?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "Returns the value and continues executing rest of the statements, if any",
                                    "Returns the value and stops the program",
                                    "Returns the value and stops executing the function",
                                    "Stops executing the function and returns the value"
                                ],
            "correct" : "Stops executing the function and returns the value",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q7: Which function among the following lets to register a function to be invoked repeatedly after a certain time?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "setTimeout()",
                                    "setTotaltime()",
                                    "setInterval()",
                                    "None of the mentioned"
                                ],
            "correct" : "setInterval()",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q8: What will happen if we call setTimeout() with a time of 0 ms?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "Placed in stack",
                                    "Placed in queue",
                                    "Will run continuously",
                                    "None of the mentioned"
                                ],
            "correct" : "Placed in queue",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q9: What will happen if the browser encounters a script tag without an src attribute?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "Throws an error",
                                    "Throws an exception",
                                    "Sends it to the compiler",
                                    "Sends it to the interpreter"
                                ],
            "correct" : "Sends it to the interpreter",
        },
        {
            "question" : "Q10: The method or operator used to identify the array is?",
            "choices" : [
                                    "isarrayType()",
                                    "==",
                                    "===",
                                    "typeof"
                                ],
            "correct" : "typeof",
        },
    ];